so going back to our many core
challenges now we have seen that the
issue of power budget splitting among
cores is solved by using a turbo
frequency when using only one core
so that a single threaded program
doesn't suffer just because it's running
in a multi-core system
pretty much then one core gets to use
all the power of the chip with some
limitations because of cooling and the
final issue that we will look at is the
confusion that all of this brings to the
operating system keep in mind that it
has to deal with multi-threading where
each core can really execute several
threads in hardware then you have cores
that can share caches then if you have a
larger system you can have multiple
chips each with its own large caches and
you can have all of these at the same
time